[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Australia the expression silvertail is used as a synonym of which of these?", "correct_answer": "Wealthy", "incorrect_answers": ["Golddigger", "Corrupted", "Hypocrite"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Aaliyahs character in Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "Trish", "incorrect_answers": ["Ashley", "Natasha", "LeMisha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finnish, the language spoken by over 94 % of the people of Finland is most closely related to this language.", "correct_answer": "Estonian", "incorrect_answers": ["Danish", "Russian", "Swedish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Cuba, the terminally ill Hyman Roth brings up the issue of Moe Green\u2019s hit, telling Michael, I didnt ask who gave the order, because it had nothing to do with business! Which movie is this from?", "correct_answer": "The Godfather II", "incorrect_answers": ["Prizzi\u2019s Honor", "Heaven Can Wait", "Dog Day Afternoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On what date did the 5 characters in the movie Breakfast Club have to sacrifice a whole day in detention?", "correct_answer": "Saturday, March 24, 1984", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturday, January 14, 1985", "Saturday, February 11, 1984", "Saturday, April 4, 1984"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following opiates is most likely to cause seizures?", "correct_answer": "Meperidine", "incorrect_answers": ["Morphine", "Hydromorphone", "Oxycodone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what type of leaves is Valdeon cheese traditionally wrapped before being sent to the market?", "correct_answer": "Chestnut leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Vine leaves", "Fig leaves", "Cabbage leaves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where are Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid when the mayor is trying organize a group to get out and kill them?", "correct_answer": "On a balcony watching", "incorrect_answers": ["Behind him", "We dont know.", "Australia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identify the 1999 movie from the quote: Decided to whip up one of my own - a group so hungry for money theyd do anything. I thought youd be more comfortable with your peers.", "correct_answer": "House on Haunted Hill", "incorrect_answers": ["The Faculty", "Deep Rising", "Stir of Echoes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Elaine Harper Brewster in the 1944 movie Arsenic and Old Lace?", "correct_answer": "Priscilla Lane", "incorrect_answers": ["Claudette Colbert", "Ingrid Bergman", "Katharine Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the same year that the first Grammy for Rap music was given, this song won for Best Song of the Year and Best Record of the Year and the singer who performed it won the Grammy for Best Performance.", "correct_answer": "Dont Worry, Be Happy by Bobby McFerrin", "incorrect_answers": ["Blessings by Betty Winan", "Fast Cars by Tracy Chapman", "Traces by George Michael"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these national costumes is closely related to Sikhism - a religion that comes from 16th-century northern India?", "correct_answer": "Turban", "incorrect_answers": ["Khalsa", "Sari", "Sayyid"]}]